[
    {
      "question": "Name the world`s biggest island?",
      "answer": "Greenland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2nd biggest country in the world?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which singer’s real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta?",
        "answer": "Lady Gaga"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to Greek mythology who was the first woman on earth?",
        "answer": "Pandora"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is known as the Land of White Elephant?",
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city was Anne Frank’s hiding place?",
        "answer": "Amsterdam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country won the very first FIFA World Cup in 1930?",
        "answer": "Uruguay"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country produces the most coffee in the world?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two countries share the longest international border?",
        "answer": "Canada and the USA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest country in the world?",
        "answer": "Vatican City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first woman to win a Nobel Prize (1903)?",
        "answer": "Marie Curie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What celebrity has their dog cloned– twice?",
        "answer": "Barbara Streisand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ludwig Van Beethoven was born in 1770 in which city?",
        "answer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
        "question": "What’s the most expensive home in the world?",
        "answer": "Buckingham Palace"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Statue of Liberty was given to the US by which country?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who invented scissors?",
        "answer": "Leonardo da Vinci"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country was the Caesar salad invented in?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which film did father and son actors Will and Jaden Smith first appear together?",
        "answer": "The Pursuit of Happiness"
    },
    {
        "question": "What planets literally rain diamonds?",
        "answer": "Saturn and Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was said to “float like a butterfly and sting like a bee”?",
        "answer": "Muhammed Ali"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cirque du Soleil started in what country?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only fruit that has its seeds on the outside?",
        "answer": "Strawberry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote songs for The Lion King?",
        "answer": "Elton John"
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. newspaper is nicknamed “the Gray Lady”?",
        "answer": "The New York Times"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first Disney animated film based on the life of a real person?",
        "answer": "Pocahontas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What character did Michael J. Fox play in ‘Back to the Future’?",
        "answer": "Marty McFly"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest lizard?",
        "answer": "Komodo dragon"
    }
]
